Wasim Khan

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India



khwasi.87@gmail.com



9987612126



linkedin.com/in/wasim-khan-bb9bb5145

Summary

Experienced as UI/UX Designer and Front End developer with industry experience designing websites, web and mobile applications.

Having professional experience working with HTML, CSS, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, wordpress Photoshop, Illustrator & adobe xd also have experience working on E-commerce, Hotel management, Money transfer, & Vehicle tracking device applications.

Worked on nabard desktop application

Frontend development

Experience

UI Designer and Developer

Dynpro India Pvt. Itd

Oct 2022 - Present (8 months)

Working for HPE as Ui designer and developer working on Tools like

Adobe XD

HTML, CSS, J Query

User Interface Designer and developer

Kha Creation USA

Jun 2022 - Sep 2022 (4 months) Working as Ui Developer and Designer

in a project base Company

Working on HTML, CSS, jQuery

using tool for design Adobe XD and Figma

Jd UI/UX Designer

Justdial

Jul 2021 - Jun 2022 (1 year)

User interface and graphic designer

• User Interface Designer(On Contract)

Quantafic Business Solutions

Nov 2020 - Jul 2021 (9 months)

UI Designer and Frontend Developer(Contract Base for 1year)

- * Working on NABARD bid project on HTML, CSS, Bootstarp, Jquery
- * UI Designing for Nabard farmer App
- * UI Designing of Axis Bank mobile application



UI Designer & Frontend Developer

Atishay Limited

Apr 2019 - Nov 2020 (1 year 8 months)

- # Understanding and designing layout using Tools like Photoshop and Illustrator
- # Designing banner and logo using Photoshop and Illustrator
- # Designing pages using HTML,CSS and Bootstrap Libraries and working function using Java script & **J**quary
- # Working on application, website designing and front end development
- # Working on wireframe and UI designing of same
- # Worked on website like E-sahyog and trackvec
- # Worked on application design and frontend development like maxidoo and zapurse
- # Changes and redesign in UI of website and mobile app of same application



Web designing and development and graphic designer

Zapmart

Jan 2017 - Apr 2019 (2 years 4 months)

- # Design banners for web, app and social media and their content.
- # Handle web design and error regarding design and functioning.
- # Consistent checkup on UI design for web and app and their up gradation.
- # Regular checking up on product prizes and offer via research via internet.



Automation / MIS Executive

Ocwen Financial Corporation - US

Apr 2014 - Jul 2015 (1 year 4 months)

- # Worked regularly on millions of customer data as our daily task which received via mail.
- # Did Task on Excel, SQL and Command prompt like (renaming, moving copying and uploading) on remote server.
- # As automation associate we also have weekly task of deleting temp data and scrap from remote server using commands and filtering those data which can be re-upload on remote server.
- # Maintaining report of daily task and work given. on excel and reporting it to team manager.

Maintaining monthly individual performance report on excel.

Education



Yashwantrao Chavan Maharashtra Open University

Master of Computer Applications - MCA, Computer Science

Nov 2021 - Nov 2023

Perusing for MCA 3 Degree in distant learning



University of Mumbai

Bachelor's degree, Business/Commerce, General 2009 - 2012

Licenses & Certifications

NIIT Diploma in Programming - NIIT Limited

Skills

Adobe Premiere Pro • Prototyping • User Interface Design • HTML5 • Bootstrap • Responsive Web Design • User Experience (UX) • User Experience Design (UED) • Wireframing • Front-end Development